{
    "id": "f46ba07215cf4444b088f87447646214",
    "title": "Reporting yes or no questions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4326e96e75ee4ce2a7e10e2ff509b903",
            "title": "Reporting Yes Or No Questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The teacher asked Raju if he ....................................... present the previous day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "has been",
                        "had been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "James asked me if I ..................................... to a zoo.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have ever been",
                        "ever went",
                        "had ever been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The master asked the girl if she .......................................... any difficulty solving the problem.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "had",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The lady asked the servant if he ............................................... her letters from the post office.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "collects",
                        "collected",
                        "has collected",
                        "had collected"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "Tom asked Ben whether a boy .................................................. a chance to whitewash a fence every day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "gets",
                        "got",
                        "has got"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I asked the boy whether his father ....................................... to the office.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has gone",
                        "had gone",
                        "went"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The girl asked if she ........................................... home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may go",
                        "went",
                        "might go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "One of them asked if they ........................................... call the police.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "can",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Della asked Madam if she .................................... her hair.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bought",
                        "will buy",
                        "would buy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The man asked the boy if he ........................................... that himself.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cannot do",
                        "could not do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}